# KATE PRASOLEK

### London E1 4RS | 07479929600

### kate.prasolek@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kateprasolek https://artekatie.github.io/portfolio https://www.behance.net/artekatie

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Adobe Photoshop CC

Adobe in Design CC

Adobe Illustrator CC

Dotmailer/ Dotdigital

Adobe After Effects

CSS3

HTML5

Bootstrap

Javascript & jQuery

Git / Github

Figma / Adobe XD

Google Web Designer

### **INTERPERSONAL SKILLS**

Eye for detail & professionalism
Can-do attitude & fast learner
Responsibility & reliability
Open mind & creativity
Commitment & consistency

Time management skills

Organisational skills

Ease of interpersonal contacts

Ability to teamwork

Customer service skills

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

A reliable, experienced in fast-paced environment designer with an easy-going, can-do attitude. Self-learner of HTML5 and CSS3.

Currently learning animations and website design. I am looking forward to working with a wide range of digital projects and consistently deliver a great experience for users and customers.

### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# Graphic Designer at Wex Photo Video, London (Feb 2018 - Jan 2020)

As a part of small in-house team, I liaised with other departments to create, according to brand guidelines, a wide range of digital and print projects, such as:

- marketing emails, website banners, social media assets, GDNs
- adverts, business cards, flyers, point of sales, posters, brochures, catalogues, pull-up banners, signage, large format prints

I was also responsible for.

- supervising magazines' schedules, liaising with publishers
- maintaining and updating templates

# Freelance Digital Designer, London (May 2016 - Feb 2018)

Creating logos, brochures, promotional digital and print assets, UI and website redesign.

## Receptionist and Research Bank Worker at Poplar Harca, London (May 2015 - Nov 2017)

Reception duties, data administration, community projects.

### Master Team Member at Paul UK (Jun 2013 - Feb 2015)

Supervising shift, organising displays and stock, handling orders, preparing sales plans & reports, customer service.

### Saleswoman at Polkomtel SA (Oct 2010 - Dec 2012)

Phone customer service duties, selling and extending contracts.

Shift Supervisor at Pizzeria laPrimera (May 2009 - Sep 2010) Organising shifts, stock, deliveries and reports.

### **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

2020 I Google Web Designer, Adobe After Effects

2018-19 | Dotmailer/ Dotdigital, Adobe Illustrator

2017 | Adobe Dreamweaver, HTML emails

HTML5/ CSS3, Javascript, jQuery

2016 Layout and Composition, Branding and Typography,

Colour for Design and Art, Graphic Design Path,

Adobe Photoshop and inDesign

2018 I Psychology, master degree